<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ReciclaIA</string>
    <string name="key_colors">Key colors</string>
    <string name="test_api">Test API</string>
    <string name="start_app">Start app</string>
    <string name="do_not_show_tutorial_again">Don\'t show tutorial again</string>
    <string name="key_colors_explanation">These are the colors generated from the user\'s wallpaper</string>
    <string name="view_based_app">View version</string>
    <string name="compose_based_app">Compose version</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="learn">Learn</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="image_for_the_item_option">image for the item option</string>
    <string name="app_info">Application information</string>
    <string name="version">Version</string>
    <string name="app_configuration">App configuration</string>
    <string name="ia_configuration">DL Configuration</string>
    <string name="should_show_tutorial">Tutorial at startup</string>
    <string name="app_theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="system">System</string>
    <string name="startup_tutorial">Startup tutorial?</string>
    <string name="dark">Dark</string>
    <string name="light">Light</string>
    <string name="start_tutorial">Launch tutorial</string>
    <string name="start_settings">At startup</string>
    <string name="startup_compose">Compose version</string>
    <string name="dl_configuration">Model processor location</string>
    <string name="remote">Remote</string>
    <string name="local">Local</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact us!</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate us!</string>
    <string name="select_image_source">Select image source</string>
    <string name="camera">camera</string>
    <string name="gallery">gallery</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="confirm_action">Confirm action</string>
    <string name="want_saving">Want to save the current data?</string>
    <string name="cancelled">Cancelled...</string>
    <string name="want_sharing_to_local_media">Do you want to save the pic in the gallery?</string>
    <string name="saved_successfully">Saved!</string>
    <string name="error_with_the_image_processing">Error processing picture!</string>
    <string name="ai_visor">AI Visor</string>
    <string name="enable_location_in_captions">Allow to include location on captures</string>
    <string name="enable_location_in_new_captions_title">Include location in captures</string>
    <string name="request_location_permission">Location permission</string>
    <string name="permission_denied_check_app_settings">Permission denied, please enable it in the app settings.</string>
    <string name="scan">Process</string>
    <string name="exported_successfully">Image saved in gallery</string>
    <string name="error_with_the_image_saving">Error saving image</string>
    <string name="data_saved">Data saved</string>
    <string name="title_of_capture">Capture title</string>
    <string name="name_the_capture">Name your capture</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="process">Process</string>
    <string name="save_data">Save capture data</string>
    <string name="save_image">Save pic in gallery</string>
    <string name="classification_result">Classification result</string>
    <string name="preditions">Predicctions</string>
    <string name="classification_information">Classification information</string>
    <string name="model_info">Model info</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="datetime">Date and time</string>
    <string name="not_classified_yet">No classification result\n Click process button!</string>
    <string name="no_camera_permission_granted">You did not authorize location permission</string>
    <string name="want_delete_all">Do you really want to delete ALL?</string>
    <string name="pattern_deleted_n_items">%s items deleted</string>
    <string name="no_results_yet">There are no classifications made, click \"+\" button below</string>
    <string name="processing_info">Waste processing</string>
    <string name="pattern_prediction_and_processing">%s (%.2f). Procesing method: %s</string>
    <string name="select_order_criteria">Select order criteria</string>
    <string name="none">None</string>
    <string name="by_tag">Tag</string>
    <string name="by_timestamp">By date</string>
    <string name="by_processing">By processing mode</string>
    <string name="desc">Descending order?</string>
    <string name="unchanged">Unchanged</string>
    <string name="by_accuracy">By accuracy</string>
    <string name="waste_information">Waste processing info</string>
    <string name="organic_container_description">Organic Waste Container (Brown) The brown container is designated for the collection of organic waste, meaning biodegradable waste of plant or animal origin. Its implementation in Spain has been expanding in recent years as part of sustainable waste management strategies.  What waste should be deposited in the brown container? This container is meant for:  Fruit and vegetable scraps.  Eggshells.  Coffee grounds and tea bags.  Bread, pasta, and rice leftovers.  Used kitchen paper and napkins.  Plant clippings and garden waste.  However, items such as used cooking oil, diapers, cleaning products, or ceramic waste should not be placed in this container.  Treatment process Organic waste collected in the brown container is transported to com</string>
    <string name="yellow_container_description">Yellow Container (Plastic Packaging, Cans, and Cartons) The yellow container is designated for the collection of lightweight packaging, such as plastics, cans, and cartons. Its use is essential for efficient waste management and promoting recycling in Spain.  What waste should be deposited in the yellow container? This container is meant for:  Plastic bottles and packaging.  Beverage and food cans.  Milk, juice, and broth cartons.  Plastic or metal lids and caps.  Clean plastic bags.  White foam trays.  However, items such as plastic toys, kitchen utensils, containers with hazardous product residues, or coffee capsules should not be placed in this container.  Treatment process The waste collected in the yellow container is transported to sorting plants, where materials are separated accordingly. Later, plastics, metals, and cartons are recycled to create new packaging, urban furniture, textile fibers, and other products. This process helps reduce landfill waste and conserve natural resources.</string>
    <string name="blue_container_description">Blue Container (Paper and Cardboard) The blue container is designated for the collection of paper and cardboard, recyclable materials that can be reused to create new products. Its use is essential for reducing deforestation and promoting the circular economy.  What waste should be deposited in the blue container? This container is meant for:  Newspapers and magazines.  Brochures and office paper.  Cardboard boxes (flattened to save space).  Frozen food cardboard packaging.  Notebooks and paper envelopes.  Cardboard rolls from toilet paper or kitchen paper.  However, items such as cartons (which go in the yellow container), laminated paper, dirty kitchen paper, or diapers should not be placed in this container.  Treatment process The waste collected in the blue container is transported to paper recycling plants, where it is sorted, cleaned, and processed to create new products such as boxes, books, toilet paper, and packaging. This process helps reduce natural resource consumption and pollution.</string>
    <string name="green_container_description">Green Container (Glass) The green container is designated for the collection of glass, a 100% recyclable material that can be reused infinitely without losing its properties. Its use is essential for reducing environmental impact and promoting the circular economy.  What waste should be deposited in the green container? This container is meant for:  Glass bottles (wine, water, soft drinks).  Food jars (jams, preserves).  Perfume and cosmetic bottles.  Glass packaging for pharmaceutical products.  However, items such as light bulbs, mirrors, window glass, tableware, or ceramics should not be placed in this container, as they require a different treatment and should be taken to a clean point.  Treatment process The glass collected in the green container is transported to recycling plants, where it is cleaned, crushed, and melted to create new containers and glass products. This process helps save energy and reduces the extraction of raw materials, contributing to environmental sustainability.</string>
    <string name="textile_container_description">Orange Container (Textile Waste) The orange container is designated for the collection of clothing, footwear, and textiles, aiming to promote the reuse and recycling of these materials. Its use is essential for reducing the environmental impact of the textile industry and fostering the circular economy.  What waste should be deposited in the orange container? This container is meant for:  Clothing in good condition or used.  Paired footwear.  Bags and textile accessories.  Sheets, blankets, and towels.  Curtains and other household textiles.  However, items such as heavily damaged clothing, carpets, mattresses, or textiles with chemical residues should not be placed in this container.  Treatment process The textile waste collected in the orange container is transported to sorting centers, where it is separated based on its condition. Clothing in good condition is directed towards reuse, either through donations or second-hand stores. Textiles that cannot be reused are recycled to create new products, such as fibers for the textile industry, insulating materials, or mattress fillings.  This system helps reduce landfill waste and optimize resources, minimizing the environmental impact of fashion and textile consumption.</string>
    <string name="rest_container_description">Gray Container (Non-Recyclable Waste) The gray container is designated for the collection of non-recyclable and non-compostable waste, meaning waste that cannot be reused or transformed into new materials. Its use is essential to prevent contamination of other containers and ensure proper waste management.  What waste should be deposited in the gray container? This container is meant for:  Diapers and personal hygiene products.  Cigarette butts.  Broken kitchen utensils.  Non-recyclable toys.  Ceramic and porcelain objects.  Pet litter and hair.  Disposable masks and gloves.  However, recyclable waste such as paper, cardboard, glass, packaging, or organic waste should not be placed in this container, as they have their own designated bins.  Treatment process The waste collected in the gray container is transported to controlled landfills or incineration plants, where it is managed safely to minimize environmental impact. In some cases, waste can be used for energy generation, although the priority remains reducing the amount of non-recyclable waste through better sorting at the source.</string>
    <string name="sigre_point_description">SIGRE Point (Medicine Recycling) The SIGRE Point is a collection system for expired or unused medicines, along with their packaging, located in pharmacies across Spain. Its goal is to ensure the safe and sustainable management of these waste materials, preventing negative impacts on the environment and public health.  What waste should be deposited in the SIGRE Point? This container is meant for:  Expired or unused medicines.  Empty medicine packaging.  Pill blister packs.  Syrup bottles and jars.  Medicine ampoules and vials.  However, items such as needles, thermometers, gauze, chemical products, or veterinary medicines should not be placed in this container, as they require different treatment.  Treatment process The waste collected at the SIGRE Point is transported to specialized management plants, where it is safely sorted and processed. Recyclable packaging is reused to create new products, while medicines are disposed of using techniques that minimize environmental impact. This system helps reduce pollution and promotes responsible medicine use.</string>
    <string name="clean_point_description">Clean Point (Special Waste Management) The Clean Point is a facility designed for the collection of special household waste, which cannot be disposed of in regular containers due to its composition or environmental impact. Its goal is to ensure proper waste management and promote recycling of these materials.  What waste should be deposited at the Clean Point? These facilities accept:  Household appliances and electronic devices.  Batteries and accumulators.  Light bulbs and fluorescent tubes.  Used oils (domestic and motor oil).  Furniture and household items.  Small amounts of construction debris.  Paints, solvents, and chemical products.  However, organic waste, lightweight packaging, paper, cardboard, or glass should not be placed here, as they have their own designated containers.  Treatment process The waste collected at the Clean Point is transported to specialized recycling plants, where it is sorted and processed according to its type. Some materials are recycled to create new products, while others are treated to minimize environmental impact. This system helps reduce pollution and promotes responsible waste management.  You can find the nearest Clean Point in Spain using the OCU search tool or the Punto Limpio platform.</string>
    <string name="specific_management_description">Special Waste Treatments (Large Waste Management) Special waste treatments include the management of bulky and hazardous waste, such as furniture, appliances, and other materials that cannot be disposed of in regular containers. In Spain, municipalities provide specific services for their collection and treatment.  What waste is managed through special treatments? These services are intended for:  Furniture and mattresses.  Household appliances and electronic devices.  Small amounts of construction debris.  Hazardous waste (paints, solvents, chemical products).  Pruning and garden waste.  End-of-life vehicles.  However, these services should not be used for recyclable waste such as paper, cardboard, glass, or packaging, as they have their own collection systems.  Treatment process Bulky waste is collected by municipal services and transported to specialized treatment plants, where it is sorted and processed according to its type. Some materials are recycled to create new products, while others are safely disposed of to minimize environmental impact. Hazardous waste is managed using specific protocols to ensure safe handling.  You can find more information about municipal waste management in Spain at AIReF and the Ministry for Ecological Transition.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_title_1">Classify the garbage</string>
    <string name="tutorial_title_2">Check your captures and stats</string>
    <string name="tutorial_title3">Learn about waste processing</string>
    <string name="tutorial_content_1">You can test how a deep learning model infers from an existing photo or by creating a new one from the app.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_content_2">You can sort screenshots and access information about them.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_content_3">Access information related to waste processing in Spain, including the types of containers available, what product goes into each container, and how to process it.</string>
    <string name="compose_sample_button_to_back_view">Compose sample, go to the main app by clicking the button below</string>
    <string name="compose_sample">Sample Compose</string>
    <string name="last_captures">Last captures</string>
    <string name="stats">Your stats</string>
    <string name="amount_captures">Amount of captures</string>
    <string name="average_confidence_in_captures">Average confidence</string>
    <string name="top3_categories">Top 3 categories</string>
    <string name="add">Añadir</string>
</resources>